- All right, state
your name and power.
- I am the Waffler, with
my griddle of justice
I bash the enemy in the
head or I burn them like so.
(skin searing)
- Ooh.
- Next.
- Hi, I am Pencil Head.
- And I am Son of Pencil Head.
- [Pencil Head] We erase crime.
- Two generations of...
- Right.
- Yes, thank you.
(arms whooshing)
(crowd screaming)
- I'd say there's potential.
♪ Somebody once told me ♪
♪ The world is gonna roll me ♪
♪ I ain't the sharpest
tool in the shed ♪
♪ She was looking kind of dumb ♪
♪ With her finger
and her thumb ♪
♪ In the shape of an
L on her forehead ♪
♪ Well the years start coming
and they don't stop coming ♪
♪ Fed to the rules and I
hit the ground running ♪
♪ Didn't make sense
not to live for fun ♪
♪ Your brain gets smart
but your head gets dumb ♪
♪ So much to do,
so much to see ♪
♪ So what's wrong with
taking the back streets? ♪
♪ You'll never know
if you don't go ♪
♪ You'll never shine
if you don't glow ♪
♪ Hey now, you're an all-star,
get your game on, go play ♪
♪ Hey now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid ♪
♪ And all that
glitters is gold ♪
♪ Only shooting stars,
break the mold ♪
♪ It's a cool place and
they say it gets colder ♪
♪ You're bundled up now,
wait till you get older ♪
♪ But the meteor
men beg to differ ♪
♪ Judging by the hole in
the satellite picture ♪
♪ The ice we skate is
getting pretty thin ♪
♪ The water's getting warm
so you might as well swim ♪
♪ My world's on fire,
how about yours? ♪
♪ That's the way I like
it and I never get bored ♪
♪ Hey now, you're an all-star,
get your game on, go play ♪
♪ Hey now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid ♪
♪ All that glitters is gold ♪
♪ Only shooting stars
break the mold ♪
("All Star" by Smash Mouth)
♪ Yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ Yo, yo ♪
(tires screeching)
♪ Hey now, you're an all-star,
get your game on, go play ♪
♪ Hey now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid ♪
♪ And all that
glitters is gold ♪
♪ Only shooting stars ♪
♪ Somebody once asked could I
spare some change for gas? ♪
♪ I need to get myself
away from this place ♪
♪ I said yep what a concept ♪
♪ I could use a
little fuel myself ♪
♪ And we could all
use a little change ♪
♪ Well, the years start coming
and they don't stop coming ♪
♪ Fed to the rules and I
hit the ground running ♪
♪ Didn't make sense
not to live for fun ♪
♪ Your brain gets smart
but your head gets dumb ♪
♪ So much to do,
so much to see ♪
♪ So what's wrong with
taking the back streets? ♪
♪ You'll never know
if you don't go ♪
♪ Go ♪
♪ You'll never shine
if you don't glow ♪
♪ Hey now, you're an all-star,
get your game on, go play ♪
♪ Hey now, you're a rock star,
get the show on, get paid ♪
♪ And all that
glitters is gold ♪
♪ Only shooting stars
break the mold ♪
♪ And all that
glitters is gold ♪
♪ Only shooting stars
break the mold ♪
(applause)